girlrising.com 2017-06-07

# Girl Rising

Ten Times Ten, LLC (“Ten Times Ten/Girl Rising,” “we,” “our,” “us”) respects your privacy. This policy describes how we collect, use, and share information related to you.

Global Internet Privacy Policy

It is our policy commitment to be transparent about our practices. This commitment reflects the value we place on earning and keeping the trust of our activists, users, viewers, employees, nonprofit and business partners and others who share their personal information with us.

This Global Internet Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes how we collect, use, and share information when you access the websites, mobile applications, or other online services that we own or operate and that link to this policy (collectively, the “Services”). As used in this Policy, the term “personal information” means information that may directly identify you personally such as name, address, telephone number, email address, etc. 

As used in this Policy, the term “aggregate information” means non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about visitors, including but not limited to age, gender, frequency of visits to the Services, parts of the Services most frequently accessed, search terms entered, browser type, IP address, etc. Aggregate information is reviewed and analyzed on a collective basis and will not be linked to the identity of any individual person. By accessing the Services, you agree to be bound by the Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Services. Each time you use the Services, the current version of the Policy will apply. 

Accordingly, when you use the Services, you should check the Effective Date of this Policy (which appears at the end of the document) and review any changes since the last version. 

Information Collected on the Services and How It May Be Used 

When you access and use the Services, there are 3 ways we may collect information about you:

Information Collected Automatically

We may collect information automatically from your device, browser, or application when you access the Services. This information typically includes, but is not limited to, the IP address of your Internet service provider, the type of device you use to access the Services, the name of your operating system (such as Macintosh or Windows) and the name and version of your browser (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome or Firefox). The information we receive depends on the settings on your web browser, device or application. We and our service providers may collect information over time and across different websites when you use the Online Services. Information Collected By Placing a “Cookie” On Your Computer We may collect information by installing a “tag” or similar technology on your device. These technologies are often called “cookies.” Our websites use cookies to collect statistical information about the ways visitors use our Services – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. We analyze this information (known as “clickstream data”) in statistical form to better understand our visitors’ interests and needs to improve the content and functionality of our websites. We may also use information collected via cookies to deliver ads based on your use of the Services. For information about how to opt out of interest-based ads, please visit <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>.

If you do not wish us to place cookies on your device, you may be able to set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit the Services, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of the Services if your browser rejects our cookies. We use GoSquared and Google Analytics to collect information about the use of the Services. GoSquared and Google Analytics collect information such as how often users visit the Services and what pages users visited prior to visiting the Services. We use this information to maintain and improve our Services. For information about how Google uses the information, see Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy. You can opt out of Google Analytics by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

  1. Information You Knowingly and Voluntarily Provide

We collect information that you provide when you use the Services, for example the information you provide when you sign up to receive email alerts, when you complete a survey, when you enter a search term on the Services, or when you ask us a question or email us with feedback. 

In some cases this information will be personal information. Girl Rising uses this information for the purposes for which you provide it. For example, if you provide your e-mail address when you sign up to receive e-mail alerts, we use your e-mail address to deliver the e-mail alerts you request.

We may also use the information we collect on the Services for various business purposes such as customer service, fraud prevention, market research, improving our products and services, and providing you with information and offers we believe may be of or interest to you. We may also remove personal information from our files and use the aggregate information for historical, statistical or scientific purposes 

Sharing/Disclosing Personal Information and Aggregate Information 

We may share, transfer or disclose your personal information collected on the Services to affiliates and other entities related to us. We may share information with service providers that provide services to us in connection with our operations (e.g., web hosting and mailing services). We may share, sell, transfer or otherwise disclose your personal information collected on the Services to third parties unrelated to Girl Rising, including charitable organizations, so these third parties can contact you for marketing and promotional purposes. Our current NGO partners are listed in the “Partners” sections of our website. These lists are subject to change. 

In addition, we may share or transfer information: (i) to comply with a legal requirement or court order; (ii) to investigate a possible crime, such as identity theft; (iii) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Ten Times Ten/Girl Rising; or (iv) when we believe it is appropriate to do so to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or others. In the event of such a sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Ten Times Ten, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the acquiring entity use personal information you have provided through this Services in a manner that is consistent with this Policy.

Security of Personal Information

We maintain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards designed to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of your personal information. Although we use security measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse, or alteration, as is the case with all computer networks linked to the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security.

Links to Third Party Internet Sites 

The Services may contain links to Internet sites or other online services that are not owned or operated by us. These links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement of the activities or content of these sites, nor any association with their operators. We do not control these third-party services, and we are not responsible for their content, security, or privacy practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on the online services you visit before using the services or providing personal information.

Access to Personal Information/Opt-Out 

If you want to have your personal information removed from our database, wish to opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties for promotional or marketing purposes, wish to update your information, or if you no longer want to receive promotional or marketing emails from us, please contact us at [tech@girlrising.com](mailto:tech@girlrising.com) or at: 

Girl Rising Global Internet Privacy Policy 114 West 26th Street New York, New York 10001

To opt out of receiving marketing emails from us, you may click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails.

Please note that while we will take reasonable efforts to honor your requests to remove personal information from our databases, some information may remain in non-operational servers, and we may retain information as we determine necessary for reasonable business purposes, including to comply with our legal obligations and to enforce our agreements.

Except as otherwise disclosed in this policy, we do not currently respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that indicate a preference for not having information collected over time and across different web sites. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in this Privacy Policy. Visit [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/) to learn more.

Retention of Personal Information 

Unless you request otherwise, we may retain personal information collected via the Services as we deem reasonable to provide the Services, products and information you request, or as permitted by applicable law.

Children and Parents

The Services are not directed to children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information on the Services from children under the age of 13.

If you become aware that your child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be deleted from our records, you may do so by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email, or contact us at [tech@girlrising.com](mailto:tech@girlrising.com) or at: Girl Rising, Global Internet Privacy Policy 114 West 26th Street New York, New York 10001.

Visitors from the European Union and Elsewhere Outside the United States

If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, your use of the Services is at your own risk and initiative and you, not us, are responsible for compliance with any applicable local and national laws. By using the Services and/or providing us with your personal information, you (i) consent to the transfers and processing of any information you provide to us, (ii) acknowledge that United States law may provide a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of various countries including, but not limited to, the European Union or your home country and (iii) understand that the Services process information under this Policy and United States law.

Questions about this Policy

If you have any questions about this Policy or our use of your personal information, please contact us at [tech@girlrising.com](mailto:tech@girlrising.com), or at: Girl Rising, Global Internet Privacy Policy 114 West 26th Street, New York, New York 10001.

Changes to this Policy 

We may update or change this Policy from time to time and without prior notice, to you by posting the revised Policy on our Services. We will post a notice on the Services to notify you of any significant changes to this Policy and indicate at the bottom of this page when it was most recently updated. If we modify or otherwise change this Policy, the modifications or changes will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy on the Services.

Effective Date: January 3, 2017

## Site Specific Screening License

### GIRL RISING

#### Multi-Screening Site Specific License

By purchasing this license, Licensee agrees to the following terms for the screening of the film Girl Rising. 

Licensor: Ten Times Ten, LLC, 125 West End Avenue, New York, NY 10023 (“TTT”).

**LICENSE:** TTT hereby grants to Licensee the non-exclusive right to screen the Girl Rising film (the “Film”) in a [private OR public] setting on or after the original screening date. The film may be screened an unlimited amount of times over the course of one (1) month ONLY at the original screening location. 

Licensee understands that any other type of use/showing of the selected Film, without the prior express written consent of TTT, and the payment of the then-applicable License Fee (which is subject to change at the discretion of TTT), is strictly prohibited. 

**LICENSING FEE:** $350

**DELIVERY:** TTT will provide Licensee one (1) DVD or Blu-Ray (to be specified by licensee) of the full film. 

**ADDITIONAL TERMS:** Licensee is granted with no rights to the ownership of the copyrighted materials contained in the DVD or Blu-Ray of the selected Film. The license granted herein is non-exclusive, non-sub-licensable or transferable, and Licensee is granted with no rights to modify or use any of the materials contained in the Film’s copyrighted materials or any trademarks or other intellectual property rights with respect to the selected Film, except as specifically set forth in this License Agreement. Licensee is not authorized to reproduce the copyrighted work or any intellectual property rights in and to the trademarks of the Film in any manner nor to prepare derivative works based upon the copyrighted work. Licensee acknowledges that the DVD provided according to this Screening License is for screening purposes only and agrees not to resell, duplicate, or make otherwise available this material.

LICENSEE WILL TAKE ALL NECESSARY STEPS TO PREVENT THE UNAUTHORIZED RECORDING AND/OR TAPING OF THE FILM BY ADMITTEES TO ANY SCREENING CONDUCTED BY LICENSEE AND WILL IMMEDIATELY NOTIFY TEN TIMES TEN OF ANY UNAUTHORIZED USE OF THE FILM BY THIRD PARTIES. LICENSEE WILL ALSO ENSURE THE DISC IS NOT DUPLICATED OR SHARED IN ANY WAY EXCEPT FOR THE PRIVATE AND PUBLIC SCREENINGS ALLOWED HEREIN. 

**REPORTING** Licensee agrees to report to Ten Times Ten the results of the screening: locations, approximate audience and any results from the screening as deemed appropriate by the Licensee. 

**MISCELLANEOUS.** Licensee shall not sell or otherwise encumber the DVD (and/or any element(s) thereof), and/or the Film, and/or any rights, under copyright and/or otherwise, therein and/or thereto. 

To the extent permissible under applicable federal laws, this Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the state of New York applicable to contracts entered into and wholly to be performed within said state. No waiver of any breach of this Agreement shall constitute a waiver of any prior, concurrent or subsequent breach, and no waiver shall be effective unless made in writing and signed by an authorized representative of the waiving party. In the event any provision of this Agreement shall for any reason be held to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable in any respect, the remaining provisions shall remain in full force and effect. 

IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have executed this Agreement as of the date first hereinabove stated.
